You, Kindaichi-run.
F'I definitely solve this case.
The famous detective!
DFCONFUSED MEMORIES , Hà G
CONFUSED MEMORIES Confused] Mlenories
43htu=7 rlhILu% Two people who doic realize, the days thc are Ilot kowI to teI
92h > Elyc{3 Wil] chase after thel.
U C Timsmojve SINEETISLIE 'Nowlitsaimeljvtheldcekdeidares .
SMonelnmnnakaniishikigzo 01 Eux Efd
G2 L Gøfezun Consciousness in my heart,
(EzeMI) JxuztUl &ut:l" Before jt slips away, ] want to see you.
akona Confused Memories 1 02
CONFUSED MEMORES Confused] Memories
Dakota higekisae nail hakono nakani 02 H779-In It @=
KakoyaSekaiwo tojikometainonakani 02
Herlsdco=s want coiclose theworld within
Sekaiwo tojikometaino 02
Yasashii namidaniTsutsumareteitai 02
Rellt Zahtuetel want to hide behind the gentle tears,
Lm) ÉMld &zI is the freedom? Where
Tve_xz#ocelJäjEz@l %<u ( 5b i7atatljslzl#(t#lll
It's here.
Disappeared?
Yeah,
Afterthat;
Finally, the exit was closed, and locked up
That is the one of the seven mysteries of Fudoh High:
1 ) a v Mile | Academy's Even Mysteries Murder Case
The forbidden biology room?
You didn't know?
You mean, there are six more?
Yeah
The second, a severed hand in the printing room
The third; the bloody fountain
The 'afterschool conjurer?"
Yeah; we don't know his identity,
No way-
B-bloodp
No, it's not.  Look
Ketchup!
Fm full.
Hajime-chan!
Thankyou!
This is my.
lask for something more tomorrow: filling
My anklel
Kindaichi Hajime; the trash of the human beings;
Hajime-chan; here.
Thank youl
You should do your own homework
If I always do it, it won't help Hajime-chan
Youlre being cheap!
You were a lot nicer in kindergarteng
No means No:
Meanie; please?
Nol
Just as usual, Kindaichi-kun:
[Sakuragi-senpaiz
Leave her alone
O-octopusg
Fm the @nly onewho understands your hidden value
Well.
Me?
I'm Sakuragi Ruiko from Mystery Research Club.
Fudou Highschool Sakuragi Ruiko Mux34 Third Year # 303
Kindaichi-kun; I want you solve it,
The Seven Mysteries of Fudoh Academy.
The Seven Mysteries?
Why are you following me, Miyuki?
don't know what you'd do, Hajime-chan!
Excuse Us..
Who are you?
Ah, I'm Kindaichi_
Sakuragi-san told me to come here
Since that Sakuragi-san scouted you;
Fudou Highschool Makabe Makoto T0uix34 22€ Third Year @jf
Ah, | thought so!
Makabe-kun is the star in mass media now.
Someone's story didn't pass even the preliminary; right?
If Matoba-sensei didn't put up my poster there,
Fudou Highschool onoue Takahiro Tuuiz34 Third Year JE =
What are you doing-?
Fudou Highschool Saki Ryuuta Tuu14 First Year 04 18 That 5 edepy ==
Sorry
Thankyou.
She's unusually clean against germs.
Somehow don't think l'Il fit in_
Anyhow, this is troublesome
No one can read this.
11 12 13 14 15 16
5 6   7   8
H-hefs right.
The club camp is held on Golden week .
easy! Easy,
Good job, Kindaichi-kun.
That's stupid.
He's the grandson of the famous detective, Kindaichi Kousuke_
He's also a genius with an IQ of 180
He has an IQ of 180?!
Today s theme is the rumored Seven Mysteries of Fudoh Academy's old school building.
You'l be killed by afterschool conjurer?
That afterschool conjurer,
Sent a threat letter to the Principal.
A threat letter from the afterschool conjurer?
You all know that we're trying to It saytear down the old school building;right? hed,
3 =
The curse..
Why send such threat?" That is our theme
Of course, we'll uncover the Seventh Mystery as well.
Well, as a guidance teacher in the Mystery Research Club,
Yes, Matoba-sensei.
Fudou Highschool Matoba Yuuichirou Toabhru ) 3  Physics Teacher AJ+2|@_ÉR
That doesnitsound like words coming from the physics teacher.
But, the problems _
You mean, you'll be responsible for anything,
Right?
M-no that{sz
Donft WoTrY:
Welll proceed with caution;
Here; look.
Mystery Research Club Meeting Minutes;
There might be a key in these to solve this mystery_
You're quite brave, Sakuragi-senpai.
1expect themost out of your capability, Kindaichi-kun.
I'm sure you'll be able to solve this mystery .
Makabe-kun, you're still here?
You're cold just as usual.
only like smart guys.
lam the Genius highschooler novelist.
If that was really your work,
Dang it, that woman!
Here, as promised.
What if someone sees this?!
If someone finds out, that'd be the end of my fame.
JC
deduction is correct, If my
Then it's
@h n@ earthquake?
To!
It finally stopped.
This building is really unstable.
see..
got it, the seventh mystery
vcø-fF7
Hajime-chan;
Sakuragi-senpai,
Why does she get close to me so much?
By any chance, am | sexy?
Hajime-chan, you are-
Ah; phone call.
Ah, Sakuragi-senpai:
Yeah, / finally get it.
The last of the seven mysteries.
Really?
Anyhow; come here right now
It was just like my deduction.
But | didn't think it'd be such a secret. scary
He'll be shocked.
The last of the seven mysteries.
wonder if she' s okay .
That s just made-up
It's creepy; the school at night.
Itwas the prinhngeron Inold days
In old days,
He died due to loss of blood
But after that,
Ever since; the sound of the hand creeping around at night
What, Hajime-chan?
No,
Please stop_
Took, behind you!
Just kidding.
Really! Hajime-chan!
Hmm?
It's dark.
You were called here too?
I'm sorry, was about to turn on the lights,
Mine was a weird male voice
A death ritual?
what are you guys doing here?! Hey;
You were called here by phone? Room
Yeah.
security Tacnidana Kyouzou 40 "a Officer i T @@
Don't say anything scary.
Hajime-chan.
Everyone; wait here.
It'Il be torn down soon
The forbidden biology room?
That's?!
Sakuragi-senpai?!
W-what?
Senpai!
Damn.
Makabe-senpai,
In this room, Sakuragi-senpai was hanged _
What's going on?
PM 9 : 42 Saki! You should help us too!
have no free hand Sorry,
It disappeared
The body and the candles..
That can't be!
All the windows are locked
Then; the thing we saw_
Somehow, doesn't this resemble the Seven Mysteries?
Hey; I think l understand what happened last night.
It was just a prank by Sakuragi-senpai.
hope that's the case
Miyuki!
Miyuki; Miyuki!
Trouble!
What?
stand aside; excuse me Hey,
1 1
Hey, you!
Sakuragi-senpai_
You.. Heyar
expect the most out of your capabilities; Kindaichi-kun:
I'm sure 'youfll be able tosolve this mystery;
Is this your doing?
This case, I'II definitely solve it.
In the name of the famous detective; my grandfather .
=
2eAJ etah  7
#+#àt(ht: #bukemieh You've taught me, such aswhere flowers bloom,
G {oEfo% %@tlnce Also the constellations and-che pain Iove brings.
E( EeL {t-bltoo<yft [3l 36*lt We talked about many things on that bench.
Uc iatltfotho1- fh~Holtt- 1found things chat | wouldn't have known by myself .
26 Stgirritoxionorrasckn heFiocJuyue
1 1 1 ~Be 3mEJ@xeltallf2 1( ( The time passes as fast as how fun things are,
Cy  1 1e( Eiio' Eaossioen Iuo tiree bewscen vouarc ( pasced Iike phe yrii @.
8 2X& #nb0l What would keep two together ,
2XcE-tt-OI thought, would be the nwvo themselves .
@anyou solve this mystery?