0 1
Nligko teiua hibigaukabe. 01
SMonelnmnnakaniishikigzo 01 Eux Efd
Suberikomu maeni aitaiyo 01
akona Confused Memories 1 02
Kakoya higekisae nai hakono nakani 02 H779-Tiy St @=
Kakoya higekisae nai hakono nakani 02 4779-Tiiy 44 m=
1 Kakoya hhigekisae nai hakono nakani 02
KakoyaSekaiwo tojikometainonakani 02
Sekaiwo tojikometaino 02
Sekaiwo tojikometaino 02 A 4n
Sekaiwoltojikometaino 02 Mriy F # X
Sekaiwo tojikometaino 02 ]
Sekaiwo tojikometaino 02
Yasashii namidaniTsutsumareteitai 02
Jiyuuwa Dokoni 02
1 04
Arlchave gaaoraalask youmneretunai? 07
But you don't look anything 08 close to deduction smart" toime.
Onoue, | could have given you one 09
Onoue, | could have given you one. 09
G0 on. 09
09 REC
10 020 21 22 23 24 25 78 729 30 1
Translator Note: The Golden Week is a collection of four 10 national holidays within seven days. In combination with well placed weekends, the Golden Week becomes one of Japan's three busiest holiday seasons, besides New Year's and the Obon week.
Translator Note: The Golden Week is a collection of four 10 national holidays within seven days. In combination with well placed weekends; the Golden Week becomes one of Japan's three busiest holiday seasons, besides New Year's and the Obon week.
1 1
3 =
A itime ago, 1 heard a student trying 12 to uncover the seventh secret went missing. longs
Translator Note: The book title is 'Mystery Research Club 12 Meeting Minutes.:' Diskette is labeled 'Seven Mysteries Report.' The 8
Translator Note: The book is titled 'Side dishes 100. 17
1 19
Mhhererdid 20
2 4
26 Belugchbuss Haa
26 Stgirritoxionorrasckn heFiocJuyue
Bokuto kisshonkoutauu 27
The real culprit is among these peoplel! 29