want you to solve the seven mysteries.
You, Kindaichi-run.
F'I definitely solve this case.
In the name of my grandfather,
3u
The famous detective!
DFCONFUSED MEMORIES , Hà G
CONFUSED MEMORIES Confused] Mlenories
43htu=7 rlhILu% Two people who doic realize, the days thc are Ilot kowI to teI
92h > Elyc{3 Wil] chase after thel.
Jle {lfusHt #tblt*0tPh< Those who lost a place to run; smile slightly .
U C Timsmojve SINEETISLIE 'Nowlitsaimeljvtheldcekdeidares .
TIME TO CRY TIME TO DIE Time to cry, Time to die
SMonelnmnnakaniishikigzo 01 Eux Efd
G2 L Gøfezun Consciousness in my heart,
(EzeMI) JxuztUl &ut:l" Before jt slips away, ] want to see you.
akona Confused Memories 1 02
CONFUSED MEMORES Confused] Memories
á#Pum#7  #0f1 Inside the box where Il9 pasc anld evel Il0 tragedy exist,
Kakoya higekisae nai hakono nakani 02 4779-Tiiy 44 m=
1 Kakoya hhigekisae nai hakono nakani 02
@peuen ~&w# Inside the box where n0 past and even nlo tragedy exist,
KakoyaSekaiwo tojikometainonakani 02
Herlsdco=s want coiclose theworld within
Sekaiwo tojikometaino 02
Yasashii namidaniTsutsumareteitai 02
Rellt Zahtuetel want to hide behind the gentle tears,
C2a @al <El Where is the freedom?
Lm) ÉMld &zI is the freedom? Where
Tve_xz#ocelJäjEz@l %<u ( 5b i7atatljslzl#(t#lll
It's here.
Disappeared?
That hanging dead body?
Yeah,
Afterthat;
A lot of students claimed to have seen the same thing.
Finally, the exit was closed, and locked up
The forbidden biology room
That is the one of the seven mysteries of Fudoh High:
1 ) a v Mile | Academy's Even Mysteries Murder Case
The forbidden biology room?
You didn't know?
The seven mysteries .
You mean, there are six more?
In that old building.
Yeah
The second, a severed hand in the printing room
The third; the bloody fountain
We know up to the sixth, but the seventh is still a mystery
They say; if you know the last one; youfll be murdered;
Bythe "afterschool conjurer:'
The 'afterschool conjurer?"
Yeah; we don't know his identity,
But the rumor says he lives in the old building:
No way-
B-bloodp
No, it's not.  Look
Ketchup!
Fm full.
Hajime-chan!
Isaw you skipped class, and just as / thought; you're at a place like this!
Miyuki, the omelet was really delicious.
Thankyou!
This is my.
lask for something more tomorrow: filling
My anklel
Ican't believe thiss
Kindaichi Hajime; the trash of the human beings;
heard he got a zero in math again:
It's hard to believe he's a childhood friend with Miyuki; one of the best students in school
Hajime-chan; here.
You already finished my homework l asked for this morning?
Thank youl
You should do your own homework
If I always do it, it won't help Hajime-chan
Youlre being cheap!
You were a lot nicer in kindergarteng
No means No:
Meanie; please?
Nol
Just as usual, Kindaichi-kun:
[Sakuragi-senpaiz
Leave her alone
Some octopus-girl that you've been hanging out.
O-octopusg
Fm the @nly onewho understands your hidden value
Well.
Me?
I'm Sakuragi Ruiko from Mystery Research Club.
Fudou Highschool Sakuragi Ruiko Mux34 Third Year # 303
Kindaichi-kun; I want you solve it,
The Seven Mysteries of Fudoh Academy.
The Seven Mysteries?
This is the first time I've visited the Mystery Research Club
Why are you following me, Miyuki?
don't know what you'd do, Hajime-chan!
I'm just watching over .
Excuse Us..
Who are you?
Ah, I'm Kindaichi_
Sakuragi-san told me to come here
Since that Sakuragi-san scouted you;
was wondering what kind of person you'd be,
Fudou Highschool Makabe Makoto T0uix34 22€ Third Year @jf
Ah, | thought so!
You're Makabe Makoto-san who was on the newspaper, right?
The one who won the mystery novel competition.
"The Dead Body Tells Everything'
It's second on the best sellers list.
Makabe-kun is the star in mass media now.
He's nicknamed, 'Genius highschooler novelist:.
Someone's story didn't pass even the preliminary; right?
If Matoba-sensei didn't put up my poster there,
Fudou Highschool onoue Takahiro Tuuiz34 Third Year JE =
What are you doing-?
Fudou Highschool Saki Ryuuta Tuu14 First Year 04 18 That 5 edepy ==
Sorry
Thankyou.
By any chance are those the plastic gloves used for operations?
She's unusually clean against germs.
Fudou Highschool akajma /oioy0 T0u 3 First Year BVaf
Somehow don't think l'Il fit in_
Anyhow, this is troublesome
What is the matter?
No one can read this.
The code that Sakuragi-senpai left.
She said, if you don't know what this means,
You cannot participate in the club camp this time.
It's just some prank that sheset up
This is just nonsense, for sure.
What, this is just club camp schedule_
If you do this, it becomes the calendar for the Golden week
11 12 13 14 15 16
H-hefs right.
The club camp is held on Golden week .
That's great; Hajime-chan!
Using matches as a multiplication symbol is the huh? key,
easy! Easy,
Good job, Kindaichi-kun.
That's stupid.
That's just pure luck
He's the grandson of the famous detective, Kindaichi Kousuke_
He's also a genius with an IQ of 180
He has an IQ of 180?!
Anyhow, let's start the club meeting
Today s theme is the rumored Seven Mysteries of Fudoh Academy's old school building.
You mean, the one that if you find out the seventh secret,
You'l be killed by afterschool conjurer?
That afterschool conjurer,
Sent a threat letter to the Principal.
A threat letter from the afterschool conjurer?
You all know that we're trying to It saytear down the old school building;right? hed,
3 =
The seven mysteries will repeat again.
If the old school building is demolished
The curse..
Why send such threat?" That is our theme
And our Mystery Research Club will solve all the problems,
Of course, we'll uncover the Seventh Mystery as well.
Well, as a guidance teacher in the Mystery Research Club,
I'd like to say something
Yes, Matoba-sensei.
Fudou Highschool Matoba Yuuichirou Toabhru ) 3  Physics Teacher AJ+2|@_ÉR
I'm worried something may 'happen to
That doesnitsound like words coming from the physics teacher.
But, the problems _
You mean, you'll be responsible for anything,
Right?
M-no that{sz
Donft WoTrY:
Welll proceed with caution;
This is alright with you; right?
8 2x7u
Here; look.
Mystery Research Club Meeting Minutes;
From 10 years ago_
found them from the storage
There might be a key in these to solve this mystery_
You're quite brave, Sakuragi-senpai.
1expect themost out of your capability, Kindaichi-kun.
I'm sure you'll be able to solve this mystery .
I'm counting on you.
Just as / thought; it's right here_
The key to solving the mystery.
It seems solving the mystery is going well.
Makabe-kun, you're still here?
You're cold just as usual.
only like smart guys.
lam the Genius highschooler novelist.
Yeah, you are.
If that was really your work,
Then it'd be wonderful
Dang it, that woman!
Here, as promised.
What if someone sees this?!
If someone finds out, that'd be the end of my fame.
JC
G/ < U J
deduction is correct, If my
Then it's
@h n@ earthquake?
To!
It finally stopped.
This building is really unstable.
W-what is this_
see..
got it, the seventh mystery
vcø-fF7
Hajime-chan;
What do you want for tomorrow's lunchbox?
Sakuragi-senpai,
Why does she get close to me so much?
By any chance, am | sexy?
Hajime-chan, you are-
Ah; phone call.
This is Kindaichi.
Ah, Sakuragi-senpai:
Yeah, / finally get it.
The last of the seven mysteries.
Really?
Anyhow; come here right now
I'll show you something interesting
It was just like my deduction.
But | didn't think it'd be such a secret. scary
He'll be shocked.
The last of the seven mysteries.
wonder if she' s okay .
The rumor says, you'll be killed by afterschool conjurer if you find that out.
That s just made-up
It's creepy; the school at night.
Itwas the prinhngeron Inold days
The second of seven mysteries is here
In old days,
A male student cut his hand off with the cutting machine in this printing room-
He died due to loss of blood
But after that,
No matter how much everyone looked, his severed hand went missing.
Ever since; the sound of the hand creeping around at night
What, Hajime-chan?
Just now, heard something weird.
No,
Please stop_
Took, behind you!
Just kidding.
Really! Hajime-chan!
Hmm?
It's dark.
You were called here too?
By that weird phone call?
You really surprised me.
I'm sorry, was about to turn on the lights,
However, you guys came in just then.
You are all here by Sakuragi-senpai's call?
Mine was a weird male voice
It said, There will be a death ritual at 10 0'clock, s0 come
A death ritual?
what are you guys doing here?! Hey;
You were called here by phone? Room
Yeah.
security Tacnidana Kyouzou 40 "a Officer i T @@
time for a death ritual . The
Don't say anything scary.
I'm taking a look around.
You guys; g0 home.
Is it okay to be with you?
Hajime-chan.
have a weird premonition
Everyone; wait here.
Well, why don't we patrol around the old school building instead of here?
feel something might happen.. like
Don't worry, you can see the old school building from this new building.
Now that / look at it this way, it does look really old.
It'Il be torn down soon
There's light
That's strange_
That light is coming from the forbidden biology room.
No one should be able to enter.
The forbidden biology room?
That's?!
Sakuragi-senpai?!
W-what?
Senpai!
I'm sure of it.
It's the biology room:
It won't open!
Where's the key?
It's called the "forbidden" biology room because there's no key.
Damn.
Makabe-senpai,
In this room, Sakuragi-senpai was hanged _
By the afterschool conjurer!
The afterschool conjurer?!
What's going on?
Hajime-chan, what's going on?
PM 9 : 42 Saki! You should help us too!
have no free hand Sorry,
It disappeared
The body and the candles..
That can't be!
Isaw it with my own eyes!
All the windows are locked
He didn't exit through the windows.
Then; the thing we saw_
What's wrong, everyone?
Somehow, doesn't this resemble the Seven Mysteries?
The disappearance of a hanged body from the forbidden biology room_
Don't say stuff like that. It can't be good omen_
Hey; I think l understand what happened last night.
It was just a prank by Sakuragi-senpai.
Shesaid she would show you something interesting; right?
hope that's the case
wonder if something happened.
Miyuki!
Miyuki; Miyuki!
Trouble!
What?
At the forbidden biology room_
Return to your classrooms quickly.
We're telling you; you cannot come in.
What the . Go back! The classes will start soon.
stand aside; excuse me Hey,
1 1
Hey, you!
This can't be.
Sakuragi-senpai_
g0 back to your classroom qui_ Hey,
You.. Heyar
expect the most out of your capabilities; Kindaichi-kun:
I'm sure 'youfll be able tosolve this mystery;
The afterschool conjurer_
Is this your doing?
This case, I'II definitely solve it.
In the name of the famous detective; my grandfather .
=
2eAJ etah  7
#+#àt(ht: #bukemieh You've taught me, such aswhere flowers bloom,
G {oEfo% %@tlnce Also the constellations and-che pain Iove brings.
E( EeL {t-bltoo<yft [3l 36*lt We talked about many things on that bench.
Uc iatltfotho1- fh~Holtt- 1found things chat | wouldn't have known by myself .
1 1 1 ~Be 3mEJ@xeltallf2 1( ( The time passes as fast as how fun things are,
Cy  1 1e( Eiio' Eaossioen Iuo tiree bewscen vouarc ( pasced Iike phe yrii @.
8 2X& #nb0l What would keep two together ,
2XcE-tt-OI thought, would be the nwvo themselves .
@anyou solve this mystery?